Guide to the Walter Thabit papers, 1950-2004
Thabit, Walter papers, 1950-2004
- Series III. Planning Projects
  - East New York (ENY)
    - ENY-73: Post Phase II Plan Approval (Box 3, Folder 15)
      After the local committee approved Phase II Plan. Communications and requests for fast action on the plan. Became clear that no further planning will take place since no support was forthcoming from central Brooklyn of the City.
    - ENY-74: Ad Hoc Committee of ENY Housing Leaders (Box 3, Folder 16)
      Establishing the Ad Hoc Committee of ENY. Vacant land survey and coverage in the media.
    - ENY-75: FHA Scandal (Box 3, Folder 17)
      News Stories of FHA (Federal Housing Authority) Scandals which shook the entire country, much of it centered on ENY.
    - ENY-76: ENY, Sunset Park, and Others Unite Against FHA Scandal (Box 3, Folder 18)
      ENY and Sunset Park and other neighborhoods join in fighting against FHA Sales of Vacant Property. Objection to the practice of foreclosing a mulit-family building and then throwing out all the tenants before putting it on sale. This is the legal battle files.
    - ENY-77: Vacant Buildings Survey, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      Results of reports included in the file.
    - ENY-78: Urban Development Corporation (Box 3, Folder 20)
      Letter of understanding with Lucas and Edward of the Urban Development Corporation regarding work in Brownsville School Analysis and Planning
    - ENY-79: Lucas and Edwards Model Cities Reports (Box 3, Folder 21)
      Could be listed as a part of ENY Phase II work. The reports were often put together with significant help from Walter Thabit.
    - ENY-80: Ocean Hill-Brownsville (Box 3, Folder 22)
      This community was so militant and anti-establishment and anti-white, they would permit no planning to take place.
    - ENY-81: Model Cities Housing Studies in Brownsville (Box 3, Folder 23)
      Model Cities Housing Studies in Brownsville by Lucas and Edwards, aided by "us"
    - ENY-82: Final Report by Lucas and Edwards (Urban Development Corporation) (Box 3, Folder 24)
      The material that went into developing the final report.
    - ENY - Miscellaneous (Box 64, Folder 34)
    - ENY - Data Requests (Box 64, Folder 35)
    - Phase I Planning (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Implementation, 1969/1970 (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Recreation (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - Phase I Reports (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - Phase I Housing (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - Vest Pocket Community Meetings (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - Landlord Meetings, Muni. Loan (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - Community Committees (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - Vest Pocket Reports (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - Model Cities Committee (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - Sponsorship, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - Training CIT. Planners (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - Model Cities Planning (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - Phase I Implementation, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - ENY School Planning Reports (Box 66, Folder 33)
    - Mental Health (Box 66, Folder 34)
    - Relocation (Box 66, Folder 35)
    - Implementation - Phase II Plan (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Brownsville Schools - UPC (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - History - Notes (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Phase II Plan (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Model Cities Reports (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Development Thrusts (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Brownsville Reports, Schools (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Industrial Quad Phase II (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Industrial Survey (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Community Organizing Questionnaire (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Pre-Phase I Plans (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Legislation (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Housing Surveys (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Various Survey Forms (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Unsafe Buildings (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Ocean Hill Proposal (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Annotative Key (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Brownsville Planning (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Contract and Background (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Central Model Cities (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Corrections (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Open Season - Index (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Style (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - Open Season - Cover (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - Photos (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - The Process of Community Destruction (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - Mapping (Box 67, Folder 28)
    - Authors' Manuscript Guidelines (Box 67, Folder 29)
    - Unity Plaza Garden (Box 67, Folder 30)
    - Administrative (Box 67, Folder 31)
    - Pratt (Box 67, Folder 32)
    - Open Season - Outline (Box 67, Folder 33)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 67, Folder 34)
    - Material for Book How East New York Became a Ghetto
      - New Book - 1st 4 Chapters, Background (Box 67, Folder 35)
      - FHA Scandals (Box 67, Folder 36)
      - Ad Hoc Committee (Box 67, Folder 37)
      - Revisited (Box 67, Folder 38)
      - WNET Programming (Box 67, Folder 39)
      - East New York Sues SHA on Vacates (Box 67, Folder 40)
      - School Planning 1 (Box 67, Folder 41)
      - School Planning (Box 67, Folder 42)
      - Chapter 2 - Background (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - Chapters 1-4 Open Season, Background (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - Schools - Background (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - Introduction (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - Planning for a Target Area (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - 5. Uniformed Services Background (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - Chapter 8 - Implementation (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - ENY CRF Remeeder (Box 68, Folder 8)
      - Cyprus Hills Development Corporation (Box 68, Folder 9)
      - Youth Chapter ENY - Background (Box 68, Folder 10)
      - Chapter 6 - Youth Background II (Box 68, Folder 11)
      - FHA Scandal – Background (Box 68, Folder 13)
      - ENY Today – Background I (Box 68, Folder 14)
      - Chapter 7 - Vest Pocket Plan (Box 68, Folder 15)
      - ENY Today – Background (Box 68, Folder 16)
      - Chapter 9 – Model Cities Fiasco (Box 68, Folder 17)
      - Chapter 15 - Problems, ENY Backgrounds (Box 68, Folder 18)
      - East Flatbush - All (Box 68, Folder 19)
      - ENY Today – Background II (Box 68, Folder 20)
      - Policing the Ghetto - Background (Box 68, Folder 21)
      - Policing the Ghetto – Background II (Box 68, Folder 22)
      - Epilogue (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - Linear Cities (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - Nehemiah (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - Central Model Cities/ENY – Last Days (Box 68, Folder 26)
  - Hartford (HFD)
    - HFD-1: Hartford Housing Program Data (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Background Information used in Developing the Housing Program.
    - HFD-2: Hartford Aug 20 Report, August 20, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      One of the Early cuts on overall housing need.
    - HFD-3: Hartford Housing Need: (Box 4, Folder 3)
      Data, memos, etc.
    - HFD-4: Hartford Community Life Association Proposal (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Greater hartford Process draft report on social and recreational services.
    - HFD-5: Hartford SAND: (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Agreement between Process and a neighborhood development group for rehabilitation, renewal and evelopment.
    - HFD-6: Upper Albany (Box 4, Folder 6)
      Development approach and background on planning effort.
    - HFD-7: Hartford- Reports, Upper Albany (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - HFD-8: Hartford- Asylum Hill/ Upper Albany Reports (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - HFD-9: Upper Albany Reports (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - HFD-10: Upper Albany (Box 4, Folder 10)
      Various Summary Technical report
    - HFD-11: Hartford- Early Childhood Libraries (Box 4, Folder 11)
      Technical Files
    - HFD-12: Hartford- Health (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - HFD-13: Hartford- Schools of Upper Albany/ Asylum Hill (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - HFD-14: Hartford- FACE Interviews (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - HFD-15: Hartford- Housing Analysis/ Background (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - HFD-16: Hartford- Recreation (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - HFD-17: Hartford Process - Upper Albany Asylum (Box 4, Folder 17)
      More technical summaries, reports
    - HFD-18: Hartford (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - HFD-19: Hartford Rehabilitation Report, Jack Dollard (Box 4, Folder 19)
      Report in great detail prepared for the Hartford City Planning Committee.
    - HFD-20: Hartford- Key file (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Hartford (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Hartford - Asylum/Albany Technical (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Hartford - Asylum/Albany Reports (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Hartford - Housing Analysis (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Hartford Key File (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Newark (N)
    - General
      - N-1: Newark Summer Project (Box 5, Folder 1)
        Disparate Materials outlining the course of affairs in this complex project which attempted to unite the two groups.
      - N-2: Newark Program Outline (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - N-3: Newark Community Union (Box 5, Folder 3)
        Newsletters and other materials produced by the NCUP (Newark Community Union Press)
      - N-4: Draft Materials - Newark (Box 5, Folder 4)
        Draft pieces of several reports pertaining to the summer project employment reports
      - N-5: New Jersey - Welfare (Box 5, Folder 5)
        Data on welfare programs; summer project.
      - N-6: Schools- Newark (Box 5, Folder 6)
        Data on schools for summer project
      - N-7: Newark Employment Report Background (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - N-8: Newark Reports - Summer (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Newark Summer Project (Box 66, Folder 14)
      - Newark Riots, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 15)
      - Newark - Gibson, 1990 (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - Newark - Tyson, Poverty (Box 70, Folder 22)
    - PEO (Planners for Equal Opportunity) Project
      - N-8a: Newark Housing Impact (Box 5, Folder 9)
        Work Program; goals, reports
      - N-9: Newark Rehabilitation Scheme (Winans) (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - N-10: Renewal- Newark (Box 5, Folder 11)
        Background on renewal in Newark
      - N-11: Newark Housing Authority (Box 5, Folder 12)
        A file of materials on the Newark Housing Authority dealing mostly with tenant relations.
      - N-12: Newark Housing Authority II (Box 5, Folder 13)
        Newark Housing Authority materials dealing with race and project data.
    - Clinton Hill, Committee on Full Employment, Poverty Program
      - N-13: Clinton Hill to 1963 (Box 5, Folder 14)
        Contains some data, examples of survey forms, maps and many news items concerning the renewal project. All that remains of Clinton Hill project/effort.
      - N-14: Clinton Hill Data (Box 5, Folder 15)
        Report copy, drafts of some sections, a few news items and neighborhood newsletters. All that remains of Clinton Hill project/effort.
      - N-15: Clinton Hill 1964- (Box 5, Folder 16)
        The continuing struggle and gradual victory. All that remains of Clinton Hill project/effort.
      - N-16: Committee on Full Employment (Box 5, Folder 17)
        Files include organization of Committee, Nyack conference on full employment and funding requests.
      - N-16a: Committee on Full Employment II (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - N-17: Committee for Miners (Box 5, Folder 19)
        Contains committee for full employment's program in eastern Kentucky where out of work miners were fighting the coal companies and fighting as well. Actions detailed.
      - N-18: Newark Poverty (Box 5, Folder 20)
        Contains Thabit's reactions to a proposed structure for the 9 Newark area boards, indicating how a planing consultant could help make it possible for the boards to develop plans.
      - Clinton Hill - Newark (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - Committee for Miners (Box 72, Folder 34)
    - Shalom Towers
      - N-19: Newark Housing Project (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - N-20: Newark - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - N-21: Site Information Options (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - N-22: Site Selection Criteria (Box 5, Folder 24)
        Environmental Impact - HUD (Housing and Urban Development)
      - N-23: Newark- Ordinance, schedules, regulations and reports (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - N-24: Shalom- Acoustic Tests (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - N-25: Newark- HUD (Housing and Urban Development) Forms (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - N-26: Shalom- Submissions (Box 5, Folder 28)
      - N-27: Newark- Closing Items (Box 5, Folder 29)
      - N-28: Seed Money- Bills, Contract, Vouchers (Box 5, Folder 30)
      - N-29: Shalom- Requisitions (Box 5, Folder 31)
      - N-30: Newark- Follow up (Box 5, Folder 32)
      - N-31: Newark News Clippings, Riots- Med School Site. (Box 5, Folder 33)
      - N-31: Newark News Clippings, Riots- Med School Site. (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Newark - Shalom Towers (Box 72, Folder 32)
  - Near East Projects
    - Abu Dhabi Amusement Park (AB)
      - AB-1: Abu Dhabi Amusement Park (Box 6, Folder 1)
        Contains key file, correspondence with client, and with various amusement ride manufacturers
      - AB-2: Train- Transportation Amusement Parks (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - AB-3: Buyers Guide (Box 6, Folder 3)
        Contains several buyers guides for rides and other attractions as well as descriptions of many.
      - AB-4: Intamin AG (Box 6, Folder 4)
        One of the world's leading designers and manufacturers of major rides.
      - AB-5: More Rides (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - AB-6: Major Attractions (Box 6, Folder 6)
        Major rides of other manufacturers. (Not Intamin AG)
      - AB-7: Amusement Park Attractions (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - AB-8: Rides- Kiddieland (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - AB-9: Abu Dhabi Resort Island (Box 6, Folder 9)
        Contains preliminary attempts to put together an approach and a consulting team to prepare designs for a resort island off Abu Dhabi
      - Abu Dhabi Amusement Park (Box 72, Folder 33)
  - Freeport (F)
    - F-1: Freeport- Census, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - F-2: Freeport- Economic Data, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - F-3: Freeport- CBD (Central Business District) Survey, RPT, ADM, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      Survey of downtown land use, our study proposal and the work program as well as some correspondence
    - F-4: Freeport- Land Use Condition Traffic Counts, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      Data on downtown land use and traffic counts in the area
    - F-5: Freeport- Land Use, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      Calculation of square ft in downtown land uses as well as conditions
    - F-6: Freeport Shopping Survey, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      A survey of 300 Freeport downtown shoppers, taken by volunteers
    - F-7: Freeport- Parking, Traffic and Circulation, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - F-8: Freeport CBD 1, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 19)
      A programming file, containing approaches, early or draft reports, early mall reports.
    - F-9: Freeport CBD Proposal 1, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 20)
      First major report on the Central Business District as well as a 701 Certification done in passing
    - F-10: Originals- Interim Reports I and II, Freeport, 1975, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - F-11: Freeport Malls- General Information and Studies, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 22)
      Research into downtown malls and mall ideas
    - F-12: Poughkeepsie, Patterson, New London, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 23)
      Reports on visits made to these malls, including Patterson
    - F-13: Freeport Malls- Specific Cities, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 24)
      Experience of many cities, from which the three above were selected
    - F-14: Freeport- Rear and Parking Plan, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 25)
      Collaborative work for improvements behind stores and to parking area
    - F-15: General- Freeport Mall, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 26)
      Final mall report and related materials
    - F-16: Freeport Press Coverage, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 27)
      Press Coverage of downtown and mall reports
    - F-17: Freeport- Department Store Analysis, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 28)
      Examines feasibility of locating a Mays Department store in downtown Freeport.
    - Freeport - Downtown Planning (Box 72, Folder 21)
    - Freeport - Phase I Reports (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - Freeport - Mall Studies (Box 72, Folder 23)
    - Freeport Mall (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - East Flatbush (EF)
    - EF- 1: East Flatbush Programming (Box 15, Folder 1)
      Approach to the study with various study outlines. Outline of recommendations and planning solutions
    - EF- 2: East Flatbush- Resident Survey I (Box 15, Folder 2)
      Contains materials on both structural and resident interview surveys. Blockfront view
    - EF- 3: Original Surveys, Est.-Int. (Box 15, Folder 3)
      Examples of how detailed interior and exterior surveys, house by house.
    - EF- 4: East Flatbush, Schools Report Suggestions (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - EF- 5: East Flatbush General (Box 15, Folder 5)
      Various materials, correspondence maps, etc.
    - EF- 6: East Flatbush- Community Facilities (Box 15, Folder 6)
      Programming for community facilities studies. Some reports and data.
    - EF- 7: East Flatbush Community Organizations (Box 15, Folder 7)
      Information on Community Organizations and on meetings we held with them.
    - EF- 8: East Flatbush- Preliminary Reports (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - EF- 9: East Flatbush Planning (Box 15, Folder 9)
      Segments of the planning activity, preliminary to the development of the draft reports
    - EF- 10: Community Participation (Box 15, Folder 10)
      Minutes of meetings, news stories of blockbusting, letters from outraged citizens and cards opposing a report recommendation to turn Holy Cross Cemetery into a park.
    - EF- 11: East Flatbush Report (Box 15, Folder 11)
      More preliminary materials used in developing the final report.
    - EF- 12: East Flatbush Final Report (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Powelton Village (PV)
    - PV-1: Powelton (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - PV-2: Powelton Village Case (Box 21, Folder 1)
      Mostly on a suit brought by a neighborhood group seeking to stop redevelopment.
    - PV-3: Powelton Report Materials (Box 21, Folder 2)
      Materials which were used to interpret the final report
    - PV-4: Powelton Report - Draft (Box 21, Folder 3)
      No draft. Just materials considered for inclusion of the final report.
    - PV-5: Powelton Village (Box 21, Folder 4)
      More materials considered for inclusion of the final report.
    - PV-6: Powelton Village - Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - PV-7: Powelton Village - Reports (Box 21, Folder 6)
      Copies of progress and final reports
    - Powelton Village Reports (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Powelton Village (Box 70, Folder 27)
  - Downtown Brooklyn (DB)
    - DB-1: Downtown Brooklyn- Background (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - DB-2: Downtown Brooklyn- Report (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - DB-3: Downtown Brooklyn (Box 21, Folder 9)
      Three draft chapters for the final report
    - DB-4: Downtown Brooklyn II (Box 21, Folder 10)
      Another four draft chapters of final report.
    - Downtown Brooklyn (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - South of Houston, SOHO (SH)
    - SH-1: SOHO- Working Papers (Box 21, Folder 11)
      Survey forms and corresponding tables
    - SH-2: SOHO Cost Data (Box 21, Folder 12)
      Rehabilitation cost estimates
    - SH-3: South Houston (Box 21, Folder 13)
      Critiques of the Rapkin report by I.D. Robbins, developer and president of the City Club
    - SH-4: SOHO- Writings, Memos (Box 21, Folder 14)
      Research and memos
    - Soho (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Poughkeepsie (PK)
    - PK-1: Poughkeepsie Programming, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      Initiating the Gate Street Rehabilitation study.
    - PK-2: Poughkeepsie- Gate St, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 16)
      Initial efforts
    - PK-3: PRS from other Cities, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 17)
      Property Rehabilitation Standards and their adjustment was a major issue. This is research on that.
    - PK-4: Poughkeepsie Traffic, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 18)
      Analysis of a street closing
    - PK-5: Poughkeepsie- Cost Estimates and Appraisals, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - PK-6: Poughkeepsie- Jefferson I, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 20)
      Progress Reports and such.
    - PK-7: Poughkeepsie- Jefferson II, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 21)
      Formal name of the project is Jefferson but it is still Gate St. More progress.
    - PK-8: Poughkeepsie- Final Report, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - PK-9: Gate St Report, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - PK-10: Jeff Amendatory, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 24)
      Work on amending the Federal Project Plan
    - PK-11: Poughkeepsie- Gate Street UR Plan Rev, 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Copy of amended plan.
    - PK-12: Poughkeepsie- Follow up, 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      Implementation Progress.
    - PK-13: Poughkeepsie- Queen City Proposal, 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Materials relating to the initiation of the project. Queen City is the formal name for Union Street
    - PK-14: Union Street Planning, 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      Early development
    - PK-15: Historic Preservation, 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Materials on Historic preservation and how it is financed elsewhere.
    - PK-16: Rehabilitation Approaches, 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      Research on rehabilitation levels
    - PK-17: Desc. Summaries; OO/AO, # Units, Wall, Condition, Architecture, Interior, 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      Descriptive summaries of survey results.
    - PK-18: Interior Conditions, 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - PK-19: Union Street Area- Existing Conditions Summary, 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - PK-20: Condition Scoring- Summaries, 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - PK-21: Union Street- Typicals, 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      Detailed summaries of a group of typical buildings
    - PK-22: Cost Estimators Writieups, Typicals, 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 12)
      Contractors rehab cost estimates
    - PK-23: Tenant Interviews- Union Street, 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - PK-24: Exp/Inc. Summary, 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      Family income vs rental cost
    - PK-25: Union Street. Survey Findings, 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 15)
      Tabulations find their way into maps and text.
    - PK-26: Poughkeepsie Schools, 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 16)
      Schools analysis
    - PK-27: Poughkeepsie Appraisals, 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 17)
      Before and after appraisals of buildings to be rehabilitated
    - PK-28: Poughkeepsie- Union Street Miscellaneous, 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - PK-29: Poughkeepsie- Final Report, 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 19)
      Materials for the final report
    - PK-30: Poughkeepsie Report, 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 20)
      Copy of final and other related reports
    - PK-31: Union Street- PURA Submission, 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 21)
      Redevelopment of agency's submission to the feds for rehabilitation of the Union Street Area.
    - Poughkeepsie - Union Street Project (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Poughkeepsie - Gate Street (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Gate St. Report (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Poughkeepsie Union St. Rehab. Feas. (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Poughkeepsie Union St. Historical Preservation (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Morningside Heights (MO)
    - MO-1: Morningside Heights, 1964-1980 (Box 22, Folder 22)
      Early volunteer involvement based on my experiences with Cooper Square
    - MO-2: MRC- Morningside- Programming, 1964-1980 (Box 22, Folder 23)
      Data and reports of items to consider or study
    - MO-3: Morningside, 1964-1980 (Box 22, Folder 24)
      Data and reports of items to consider or study. Early reports
    - MO-4: Interoffice Memos, HAD, 1964-1980 (Box 22, Folder 25)
      Materials from the Housing and Development Administration of the City.
    - MO-5: Miscellaneous Programming, 1964-1980 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - MO-6: Morningside- West harlem, 1964-1980 (Box 22, Folder 27)
      Material on West Harlem renewal needs. One of the competing interests which plaed a major role in Morningside Planning
    - MO-7: Morningside- SROs, 1964-1980 (Box 22, Folder 28)